elections.in 2018-12-29

# Privacy Policy - Elections.in

www.elections.in (hereinafter collectively referred to as "Elections.in") respects your privacy and committed to ensure that your privacy is protected by means of protecting your personally Identifiable Information you share with us. Personally Identifiable Information is information by which a person can be identified such as name, address, telephone number, SSN, e - mail ID and date of birth. 

Should this Website ask you to provide Personally Identifiable Information when using this website, you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Website never stores your access credentials (User-Name and Password) of your social media accounts on its servers, while you are accessing services of this Website. 

This Website may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page periodically to ensure that you are comfortable with any changes. This policy was last updated on October 15th 2013. 

**What this Website Collects**

  * This Website may collect Personally Identifiable Information.
  * This Website may use 'cookies' and 'web beacons' to manage your status and verify your identity.
  * This Website may collect geophysical IP Address/browser information/other technical information for system and server administration. 
  * This Website may collect other information relevant to surveys and offers. 

**What does this Website do with the information Collected**   
This Website requires this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons: 

  * To fulfill the services you have asked this Website to perform.
  * For internal record keeping.
  * To improve this Website products and services.
  * This Website may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.

**With whom this Website shares the information**  
As a thumb rule, this Website will not willfully disclose your Personally Identifiable Information with any third party except under following conditions - 

  * When Information is forwarded to Service Providers to fulfill the services you have asked this Website to perform.
  * When this Website is legally compelled to provide the information to the Law Enforcement Authorities or government regulatory or administrative or similar agency as part of a judicial or administrative proceeding to disclose the Information.

**Security**  
This Website is committed to ensure that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure this Website has put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information this Website collects online. While this Website strives to protect your personal information, this Website can not ensure or warrant total security of any information you transmit over the transmission medium. 

**Limitation of Liability**  
This Website may contain links to other websites or advertisements which drive you to another website. However, once you have used these links to leave this Website website, you should note that this Website does not have any control over that other website. Therefore, this Website cannot be held responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites as such sites are not governed by this Privacy Policy. You should exercise caution and look at the Privacy Policy applicable to the website in question. 

Kindly see [Disclaimer](http://www.elections.in/disclaimer.html) also. 

Last Updated on 10/15/2013
